http://budgetrac.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Our Commitment To Privacy: Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.
Information Collection & Use: The Company may request the provision of individually identifiable information to order products and services from the Company. The data request may include certain personal and financial information about you including, but not limited to, your name, shipping address, email address, telephone and fax numbers, and credit card information.
The Company collects this individually identifiable information to complete business transactions, administer individual accounts, deliver marketing material provide customer support and meet government regulatory requirements such as tax collection.
The Company will not monitor, edit, disclose, sell, rent, license, exchange, or release any of your personally identifiable information without your explicit consent unless the Company has reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary: (a) to conform to the edicts of law or comply with legal process served on the Company; (b) to prevent injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the Company rights or property, other Users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities; or (c) to act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of the Users or the public. User acknowledges that it is the Company policy to respond to all governmental inquiries. If the Company transfers assets, sells the line of business relevant to this privacy statement or has any change in control, User information may be transferred to the entity that acquires such assets or control of the Company. Security: the Company takes every precaution to protect our Users’ information. When Users submit sensitive information via a website, your information is protected both online and off-line. Information collected by the Company is stored in secure, locked operating environments that are not available to the public. We have firewalls for both our web server and internal network. All of our employees are dedicated to maintaining and upholding your privacy and security and are aware of our privacy and security policies. Only employees who require information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use the utmost discretion when accessing personally identifiable information. They may not, at any time, use this information for purposes outside their marketing functions. Any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and reminded about the importance we place on privacy.
Access: We give Users access to personally identifiable information in order to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate information by sending an email to support@budgetrac.com. Log Files and Sharing of Info: the Company uses your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information. IP addresses are also used to provide an audit trail in the case of attempted illegal use of the site as well as to guard against spamming.
Cookies: “Cookies” are pieces of information that a web site transfers to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify Users, although they do identify a User’s computer. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you’d prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of a web site if you do so. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your Password so that if you choose to, you do not have to re-enter your password each time you visit our site. Advertisers that display ads on our site may also use cookies. the Company does not have access to the information obtained from those cookies.
Changes to Privacy Policy: the Company reserves the right to change this policy at any time without notice. The amended policy shall be effective immediately after they are initially posted on this Site. User’s continued use of the Site after the posting of the amended Terms on the Site constitutes User’s affirmative: (a) acknowledgement of the Terms and its modifications; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by the Terms, as amended.
Contact Us: If you have any questions regarding this privacy statement, the practices of the Company or your dealings with our web site, please contact us at:
Budgetrac
211 E. Lombard St
Suite 301
Baltimore, MD  21202
Support: support@budgetrac.com
Sales: sales@budgetrac.com
